The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
It's you !
Fellow cultivators, stop !
Explode !
Today,
you won't escape me !
Red Butterfly's cultivation is too high
and she displays such a strong killing intent.
If I want to survive
I must also attack.
Wang Lin's\NRestriction Spear
Ceng Niu's is Early stage Soul Formation,
how can he display such strength !?
Red Butterfly,
you didn't send your parents off.
You are unfilial !
He actually knows how to break her Dao Heart,
that's unexpected.
For one selfish desire,
you destroyed the Four Sect Alliance.
You are heartless !
You...
You tried to kill me without any reason.
That is unjust !
Xue Yue still exists
yet you sold yourself to Suzaku.
You are unfaithful !
You are unfilial, unjust, and unfaithful !
What kind of Dao are you cultivating ?!
Even when all the stars align,
I still can't even touch her.
You are the first one
who forced me to use my life artifact.
You can rest in peace now !
Stop !
Fellow cultivator Red Butterfly,
Brother Ceng,
I was the one who invited you here.
If you both continue,
then don't blame me for being ruthless !
Fellow cultivator Chi Hu,
I'm not the one who started all this.
This has nothing to do with you.
Back down !
Fellow cultivator Red Butterfly,
both of you are my guests.
If you insist on continuing to attack,
then that means you’re hostile towards me !
I will stand with Brother Ceng and fight back.
And if I make it back alive,
Chi Hu's\NOrigin Soul
I’ll definitely report this to Xi Zu !
Divine Retribution !
Okay.
Chi Hu,
for the sake of our relation,
I won’t kill this person today.
But the celestial jade coffin
must be mine.
Red Butterfly,
do you really think
that I can't kill you ?
I only need to send out this restriction in my hand
and this fragment will collapse.
Do you believe me ?
Brother Ceng,
I’ll make the decision.
Everything we obtain
will be split equally between us.
How is that ?
Good,
I leave it to Brother Chi Hu then.
Ceng Niu,
when we return to planet Suzaku,
do you dare to fight me ?
I'm willing.
Ting'er,
look,
Ting'er
we are home.
It has been 1000 years
and you are still so beautiful.
Your body was preserved
thanks to the celestial jades I gathered.
You kept your beautiful appearance.
I will definitely find
more celestial jades for you.
People say I'm a crazy, disgusting,
corpse-loving maniac.
They don't understand
that it is fate that I met you in the Celestial Realm.
Who cares if they say I'm crazy.
I don't regret it.
Don't be afraid.
Your husband will always protect you.
will die.
Anyone that opposes us,
Celestial Jade Pagoda
Fellow cultivator Red Butterfly's ice sculpture really is amazing,
I admire you.
This fragment
is the coldest of the Celestial Realm.
Central Cold Fragment\NRain Celestial Realm
Without fellow cultivator Red Butterfly,
we couldn't have crossed those lands of ice.
Even if it is beyond this obstacle,
why hasn't anyone else
found the location in the jade ?
To tell you the truth,
the reason I'm so confident
is because that fragment cannot be accessed through the vortex.
It's a very rare case of fragments overlapping.
Even teleportation formations are useless there.
How did Xi Zu find it back then ?
This involves my clan's secrets,
I can’t tell you.
After traversing this cold fragment,
we will have to go through the void.
After the void,
we will reach the overlapping fragment.
I have done my job,
this is the end of the fragment.
My spiritual energy has ran out.
From now on,
I won't act anymore.
Don't worry fellow cultivator,
you can count on us now.
You have spent a lot of spiritual energy these past 3 days
so you should get some rest.
Even if she ran out of spiritual energy,
she can just take a pill to recover it.
She clearly is luring me into attacking her.
If I could reach Middle stage Soul Formation,
my domain would evolve
and I would be able to defeat her.
100 years to Soul Formation,
she might be a genius
but her cultivation must be unstable.
The Giant Demon Clan's treasure,
the star compass ?
Fake Star Compass
In Tu Si's memory,
I have the method to craft such a star compass.
It's a pity most of the materials are extinct
so it's almost impossible to use.
If it were a real star compass,
I would not be able to control it with my cultivation.
This one is just an imitation
so it's not as effective as a real one.
Red Butterfly,
please go to the west side of the compass, under the defensive barrier.
That way you can safely recover your spiritual energy.
I promise you that
nothing will bother you
during this trip through the void.
Brother Ceng,
I need you to control the eastern side.
In this void,
there are many unknown entities.
You need to use those souls of yours to scout
and if you encounter anything,
tell me so I can avoid it.
In this void,
you must not spread your Divine Sense
because doing so will bring about disaster.
This is something
Ancestor Xi Zu told me.
Brother Chi Hu,
this compass
is meant to be operated
by at least 5 people.
Correct !
But there aren't enough treasures
to divide between 5 people.
Brother Ceng,
if this compass
breaks in the void,
none of us will survive.
I must focus all of my attention on controlling the compass
so it will all depend on Brother Ceng.
Void\NRain Celestial Realm
There's something 10 li ahead.
Hurry up ! Let's go !
Thank you Brother Ceng for the early warning.
Without you,
the three of us
would have died there.
What kind of beast was that ?
I have no idea
but something that can live inside the void of the Celestial Realm
is not something we can handle.
This beast is called Xu.
This Xu is considered a minor destructive beast.
It is born from devouring the earth
Xu
and lives by feeding off Yin energy.
Even during ancient times,
the ancient cultivators
would need many people
to defeat it.
Brother Ceng is really knowledgeable,
I admire you.
Who knows if what he said is real ?
Don't make up a random name.
Ignorant.
You !
This beast only spreads its tentacles
when it's looking for food.
When this beast hunts,
it spreads out a red aura.
It's not something we can resist.
Brother Hu,
quickly fly north !
But...
if we got further north,
we will be even more lost in the void.
I don't believe him,
if we continue north here,
our future will be uncertain.
It's pointless to talk about this !
Brother Ceng !
It's fine that he left.
I don't believe
that he recognized that creature.
Brother Ceng was right...
Had I listened to Brother Ceng,
this wouldn't have happened.
Go faster !
Red Butterfly, do something !
Red Butterfly !
The lost petals
can be recovered via cultivation.
But I only have 5 stamens...
I will never be able to get it back !
Brother Ceng,
sit down so we can talk.
I know I was wrong before,
I apologize for my mistake.
Is there anything else the beast will do ?
How can we choose our direction after this ?
Since we've escaped the red aura,
there shouldn’t be any issues for now.
Brother Chi Hu should follow the map
and try to get back on track.
Okay.
The star compass has been damaged...
It won't last long in this condition.
We need to speed up.
From now on,
I need to completely rely on him.
10 days later
We've been through a lot in the past 10 days.
Thank you, Brother Ceng.
You're welcome.
I have also gained a lot from
our discussions about the Dao.
The Giant Demon Clan isn't native to planet Suzaku.
My ancestors moved there
thousands of years ago.
It's natural that our techniques
are somewhat different.
That's...
Golden Purple Stone
Brother Chi Hu,
please wait a moment.
This stone is used to refine star compasses.
In order to leave planet Suzaku,
I will need my own star compass.
Void near the first layer of\Nthe overlapping fragments\NRain Celestial Realm
We were waiting on the star compass for you to come back
but it began to shake violently
and a strong force threw us off of it.
In Tu Si's memory,
I have a way to repair it.
The star compass is badly damaged,
it's unusable.
It cannot help us fly anymore.
The three of us will have to rely on ourselves.
In 3 days,
we should arrive at the fragment.
I feel like we are being followed.
3 days later
This is it,
this is the place.
Xi Zu once described the first layer to me.
Brother Chi Hu,
since the location on the jade
seems to be on another layer,
which layer is it on ?
Useless question.
Of course it's on the second layer.
It is already very unlikely for fragments to overlap once.
Ignorant.
Brother Ceng,
it's on the second layer.
But my ancestor Xi Zu once speculated
that there might be a third layer below.
Let's move, follow me.
Ting'er,
don't worry.
There must be more celestial jades on the third layer.
This...
Second layer of the\Noverlapping fragments\NRain Celestial Realm
Was Xi Zu mistaken ?
Where are the coffin and the celestial swords ?
How could they have vanished ?
Is this the place you were talking about ?!
If you don’t give me a proper explanation,
I won't let this go !
Chi Hu doesn't seem to be lying.
Something's wrong here.
Instead of arguing, why don't
we do something ?
You two,
I was too reckless.
I didn't expect that...
You were reckless ?
Will saying that help me recover my lost stamen !?
If you don't explain yourself,
then don’t blame me for not caring about our clans’ relationship.
Once we return to planet Suzaku,
I'll give you a proper explanation.
I, Chi Hu, am the young master of the Giant Demon Clan.
Although I can’t match you,
I’m a man of my word.
Brother Chi Hu,
you said before that there might be a third layer.
I think that...
I have found the entrance.
Five Elements Sect's Zhou Yi ?!
Falling from the night sky and melting into dust\Nlike water without a source.
Like the difference between clouds and mud,\Nthe truth cannot be found in conflict.
Life and death\Nare like the moment when the rain falls
and like many other unseparable things.
In this lifetime,\Nto cultivate the truth, cultivate the world first.
Old grudges had to be settled\Nbecause half an inch is engraved into my tree rings.
Use the most vivid love and hate\Nto ask questions to your fate.
Let your eyes be filled enough with rage\Nto pierce the heart and the soul
then soften because of the mortals' fireworks.
Only when you bend down can you understand\Nthe hidden edge of the blade.
The human mind is nature,\Nthe rain fell silently like an answer.
Life and death are just moments away,\Nthere are many other solutions to grudges.
Use your dusty heart\Nto depict the world.
One stroke is for killing.\NAfter struggling for hundreds of years, I endured letting go.
One stroke is for caring.\NEverywhere there is life, there are thousands of lights.
Give up your mind to be refined\Nby this endless world.
The human mind is nature,\Nthe rain fell silently like an answer.
Life and death are just moments away,\Nthere are many other solutions to grudges.
Use your dusty heart\Nto depict the world.
One stroke is for killing.\NAfter struggling for hundreds of years, I endured letting go.
One stroke is for caring.\NEverywhere there is life, there are thousands of lights.
Give up your mind to be refined\Nby this endless world.
Snow falls as my hair turns white, winter withers\Nwhile prosperity sprouts in summer.
I step into the world, with light at my fingertips,\Nthe law of cause and effect.
I observe the vastness of heaven and earth so I can get rid of evil.
Obsession arises from one thought, life and death arise from one thought.\NReincarnation is not to be feared.